Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part III WAG.025.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Operations and Subject Files, 1903-2007
  - Middle East: Memos, 1957-1959 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Middle East: Palestine Liberation Organization, 1974-1979 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Middle East: Peace Process, 1977, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Middle East: Senate Debate, 1958-1959 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Middle East: Sisco Meeting, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Middle East: U.S. Government Involvement, 1955-1963 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Migrant Labor, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Milgram, Morris, 1969-1971 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Milwaukee, WI, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Minimum Wage, 1965-1966 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Minimum Wage, 1973-1977 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1964 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Minkoff, Isaiah, 1974-1976 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Minkoff Luncheon, 1979 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - Minnesota, 1960-1966 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Minnesota, 1969-1978 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Minnesota: Correspondence, 1957-1971 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - Missouri, 1965, 1974-1975 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Mitchell Breakfast, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Mlotek, Yosl (Joseph), 1963 (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - Monroe (North Carolina) Defense Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 152, Folder 30)
  - Mont, Max, 1959, 1973 (Box 152, Folder 31)
  - Montgomery (Alabama) Anniversary Concert, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 32)
  - Morgenstern Article, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 33)
  - More Effective Schools Program, 1963-1967 (Box 152, Folder 34)
  - Moch, Jules, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Modern Community Developers, 1966 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Summary of Activities, Undated (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, Undated (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1956-1957 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1961-1962 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1963-1969 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1970-1976 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Muravchik Biographical, 1970 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Muravchik: Congratulatory Notes, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel: Correspondence, 1963-1978 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Muravchik Luncheon, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Muravchik: "My Credo as a Jew", 1962 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Muravchik, Emanuel: Review of V. Meed On Both Sides of the Wall, Undated (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Muravchik: "Troubled Allies", 1963 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Narkiss, Uzi, 1979-1980 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Nashville, TN, 1960-1961 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Nasser, Gamel Abdel, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 18A)
  - National Alliance for Safer Cities, 1972-1974 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - National Alliance of Postal Employees, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1964-1977 (Box 153, Folder 21-22)
  - National Black Political Convention, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - National Captive Nations Committee, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1970 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1964-1967 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1968-1971 (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - National Committee against Discrimination in Housing, 1963-1965 (Box 153, Folder 29)
  - National Committee against Discrimination in Housing, 1966 (Box 153, Folder 30)
  - National Committee for Fair Representation, 1964-1965 (Box 153, Folder 31)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel, 1964-1975 (Box 153, Folder 32)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 33)
  - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, 1963-1969, 1973-1979 (Box 153, Folder 34-37)
  - National Conference on Religion and Race, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 38)
  - National Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 39)
  - National Education Association, 1963-1966 (Box 153, Folder 40)
  - National Executive Board (JLC), 1965-1989 (Box 153, Folder 41)
  - National Executive Committee (JLC), 1959-1960 (Box 153, Folder 42)
  - National Executive Committee (JLC), 1970-1977 (Box 153, Folder 43)
  - National Executive Committee and Administrative Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - National Executive Committee: Memos, 1960-1963 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - National Executive Committee: Memos, 1969-1970 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1961-1963 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - National Health Security, 1971-1974 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC), 1972-1989 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1959, 1963-1965 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - National Labor Service, 1963-1966 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - National Program Committee, Jun 1978 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - National Program Plan, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1957-1959, 1962-1963, 1966-1968 (Box 154, Folder 11-15)
  - National Socialist White Peoples Party, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - National Spinning Co. Strike: North Carolina, 1963-1967 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - National Staff Conference, 1975-1977 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - National Student Association, 1966-1967 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - National Trade Union Conference on Civil Rights, 1956 (Box 154, Folder 19A)
  - National Urban League, 1957-1974 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Nazi Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Nazi War Criminals, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Nazis: American, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Nazis: Justice Department Files, 1982-1987 (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - Nazis: Statute of Limitations, 1978-1980 (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - Nebraska, 1963-1966 (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - Negro American Labor Council, 1964-1966 (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - Negro Labor Committee, 1957 (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - Nestle Boycott, 1977-1984 (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - Netherlands, 1957-1959 (Box 154, Folder 30)
  - New Bedford, MA, 1957-1963 (Box 154, Folder 31)
  - New Haven, CT, 1957-1958 (Box 154, Folder 32)
  - New Haven, CT, 1959-1960 (Box 154, Folder 33)
  - New Haven, CT, 1961 (Box 154, Folder 34)
  - New Haven, CT, 1975-1976 (Box 154, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey, 1957-1966 (Box 154, Folder 36)
  - New Jersey: Labor, 1960-1964 (Box 154, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey: State Industrial Union Dept., 1964 (Box 154, Folder 38)
  - New Left, 1965-1971 (Box 154, Folder 39)
  - New Politics Coalition, Undated (Box 154, Folder 40)
  - New Politics Convention, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 41)
  - New Politics: Langley Article, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 42)
  - New South Student: Labor Edition, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 43)
  - New University Thought, 1966-1967 (Box 154, Folder 44)
  - New York Citizens Committee for Public Higher Education, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 45)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1962-1971 (Box 154, Folder 46)
  - New York City Chapter (JLC), 1963-1974 (Box 154, Folder 47)
  - New York City Chapter (JLC): Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 154, Folder 48)
  - New York City Chapter (JLC): Social Evenings, 1963-1964 (Box 154, Folder 49)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights, 1965-1969 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - New York City Commission on Intergroup Relations, 1957-1958 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - New York City Committee on Jewish Affairs, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - New York City School Boycott, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 3A)
  - New York Committee on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - New York Jewish Community Relations Council, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - New York Membership Division, 1962 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - New York Police Dept.: Felicia Shpritzer, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - New York State, 1957-1966 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - New York State Attorney General, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - New York State Commission against Discrimination, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - New York State Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1963-1964 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Newark, NJ, 1957-1961 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Newark Teachers Strike, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - News Clips (JLC), 1961-1974 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - News Service, 1957-1959 (Box 155, Folder 14A)
  - Nixon's Economic Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Nominations Committee, 1967-1982 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Norman Fund, 1962, 1969 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Norman Thomas High School, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Northern Student Movement, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Norway, 1957-1964 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Norway: Haakon Lie, 1973-1974 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Novak, Michael: "The New Anti-Semitism", 1974 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Novogrodsky, Emanuel, Undated (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Oakland, CA, 1955-1966 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA): Schweiker Bill, 1978-1980 (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Office Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Office Committee, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Office Committee, 1964-1971, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Office Committee: Memos, 1970-1973 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1959-1965, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Office of Federal Contract Compliance, 1971-1972 (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Office Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Officers Meetings, 1969-1972 (Box 155, Folder 34)
  - Offshore Drilling, 1976-1978 (Box 155, Folder 35)
  - Ohio, 1957-1981 (Box 155, Folder 36)
  - Oil Industry: Issues, 1974-1978 (Box 155, Folder 37)
  - Olympics, 1973-1980 (Box 155, Folder 38)
  - Omaha, NE, 1957-1962, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 39)
  - O'Neal, Frederick, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 40)
  - Oneita Boycott, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 41)
  - Organization for Rehabilitation through Training (ORT), 1960-1981 (Box 155, Folder 42)
  - Orkin Cocktail Party, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 43)
  - Ostroff, Harold, 1981-1984 (Box 155, Folder 44)
  - "Our Union Heritage", 1964-1965 (Box 155, Folder 45)
  - Overseas Activities: JLC, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 46)
  - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO), 1974 (Box 155, Folder 47)
  - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO), 1979-1988 (Box 155, Folder 48)
  - Palestine National Council, 1977 (Box 155, Folder 49)
  - Papanek, Ernst, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 50)
  - Pat, Jacob: Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 155, Folder 51)
  - Pat, Jacob: Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 155, Folder 52)
  - Pat, Jacob: Death of, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 53)
  - Pat, Jacob: Memorial, 1967 (Box 155, Folder 54)
  - Pat, Jacob: Testimonial Dinner, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 55)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1967-1969 (Box 155, Folder 56)
  - Patt, Emanuel, 1959-1965 (Box 155, Folder 57)
  - Pen Club, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 58)
  - Penn South Meetings, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 59)
  - Pension Fund (JLC), 1973 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Peres, Shimon, 1980 (Box 156, Folder 1A)
  - Peretz Farlag, 1970 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Peretz, Martin, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Permanent Replacement Workers, Undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Personnel, 1963-1965 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Pesotta, Rose, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 5A)
  - Petition Drive, 1965-1967 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Phelps Dodge, 1984 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia, 1957-1981 (Box 156, Folder 8-15)
  - Philadelphia Jewish Experiment: Union Labor Dispute, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Philadelphia Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Phoenix, AZ, 1957-1959 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Phoenix, AZ, 1960-1967 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1957-1960 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1961-1966 (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1967-1978 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - Pittsburgh Plan, 1970 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - Plant Closings, 1979-1980 (Box 156, Folder 24)
  - Poale Zion and Farband Labor Zionist Order: Proposed Merger with JLC, 1968-1969 (Box 156, Folder 24a)
  - Point of View, 1961-1963 (Box 156, Folder 25)
  - Point of View, 1964-1966 (Box 156, Folder 26)
  - Point of View, 1967-1971 (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - Point of View: Comment, 1961-1963 (Box 156, Folder 28)
  - Point of View: Proposal, 1968-1970 (Box 156, Folder 29)
  - Poland, 1957-1962 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Poland, 1963-1969 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Poland, 1980-1983 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Poland: Aid, 1959-1963, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Poland: Claims, 1957-1959 (Box 157, Folder 4A)
  - Poland: Correspondence: A, 1957-1959 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Poland: Correspondence: B, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 6-7)
  - Poland: Correspondence: C, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Poland: Correspondence: D, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Poland: Correspondence: E, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Poland: Correspondence: F, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Poland: Correspondence: G, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Poland: Correspondence: H, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Poland: Correspondence: I, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Poland: Correspondence: J, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Poland: Correspondence: K, 1957-1959 (Box 157, Folder 16-17)
  - Poland: Correspondence: L, 1957-1959 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Poland: Correspondence: M, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Poland: Correspondence: N, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Poland: Correspondence: O, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Poland: Correspondence: P, 1957-1959 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Poland: Correspondence: R, 1956-1959 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Poland: Correspondence: S, 1956-1959 (Box 157, Folder 24-25)
  - Poland: Correspondence: T, 1957-1958 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Poland: Emigration, 1968-1969 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Poland: Opposition to Warsaw Ghetto Commemoration, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Police, 1959 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Police, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Polish Anti-Semitism, 1957, 1968-1970, 1983, undated (Box 158, Folder 5-9, 9A)
  - Polish Anti-Semitism: Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Polish Anti-Semitism: Publicity, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Polish Refugees, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Poor Peoples Campaign, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Portnoy, Samuel, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Post-War World Council, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Poverty, 1960-1967 (Box 158, Folder 16-17)
  - Poverty: Jewish, 1970-1976 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Poverty Rights Action Center, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr., 1967 (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Prayer in Public Schools, 1959-1961 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Prayer in Public Schools, 1962-1963 (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 24)
  - Preferential Treatment: Symposium, 1964 (Box 158, Folder 25)
  - President's Commission on the Holocaust: JLC Statement, Undated (Box 158, Folder 26)
  - Press Associates, Inc., 1957 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1957-1959 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1963 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1964-1965 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1966-1970 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1971-1978 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1979-1983 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1984-1988 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases: Yiddish, 1961-1968 (Box 159, Folder 10-15)
  - Prime Ministers Conference (Israel), 1968-1969 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers (PATCO): Strike, 1981 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Program (JLC), Undated (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Program Plans, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Progressive Alliance, 1979-1980 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Progresso (Newspaper), 1974 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Providence, RI, 1957-1962, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Public Accommodations, 1959-1963 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Public Education and Religious Liberty, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Public Employees, 1970-1971 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Publicity, 1972-1989 (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - Publicity Outlets, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Publications Committee, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico, 1957, 1963 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Quotas, 1963 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Racolin, Alexander, 1967 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Racolin Fund, 1959-1963, 1967, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 6-7)
  - Radical Zionist High School Union, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Radio and Television, 1963-1965 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Radio and Television, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Radio Liberty, 1967-1968, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Radio Program: "Report on Freedom", 1964-1967 (Box 160, Folder 12-14)
  - Randolph, A. Philip, 1959-1969 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Rapoport, Bernard, 1977-1980 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Reapportionment, 1965-1966 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Reconversion, 1964 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Refugee Aid, 1959 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Refugee Aid, 1963 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - Rehnquist-Powell Supreme Court Nominations, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Religion and Labor Foundation, 1963 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Religion and Public Schools, 1956-1961 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Religion and Public Schools, 1962-1964 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Religion and Public Schools: America Editorial, 1962 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Religion and Public Schools: Bible Readings, 1962-1964 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Religion and Public Schools: Christmas-Hanukah, 1956-1962 (Box 160, Folder 27)
  - Religion and Public Schools: School Prayer, 1959-1964 (Box 160, Folder 28)
  - Religious Action Center, 1975-1976 (Box 160, Folder 29)
  - Reparations: Argentina, 1958-1961 (Box 160, Folder 30)
  - Reparations: Austria, 1959-1960 (Box 160, Folder 31)
  - Reparations: Belgium, 1961-1962 (Box 160, Folder 32)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference, 1957-1959 (Box 160, Folder 33-35)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference, 1960-1966 (Box 161, Folder 1-11)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Applications, 1957-1959 (Box 161, Folder 12-15)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Applications, 1960-1962 (Box 162, Folder 1-3)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Individuals, 1957-1964 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Literature, 1960 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Literature Committee, 1957 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Publications Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 162, Folder 7-8)
  - Reparations: Claims Conference-- Report of the Study Committee, 1958 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Reparations: France, 1959 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Reparations: Germany, 1963-1965 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Reparations: JLC Role, 1960 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Reparations: Mason, Malcolm, 1965 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Reparations: United Registration Office, 1963 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - Reparations: United Restitution Office, 1962 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - "Report on Freedom", 1966-1967 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - Reports, 1960-1965 (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - Reports, 1969-1979, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Reports: National Director, 1964-1967 (Box 162, Folder 20)
  - Rescue Project: Fortieth Anniversary, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Rescue Project: Fortieth Anniversary-- Biographies, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1967 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1969-1979 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions Committee, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions: Various Labor Organizations, Undated (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions: Various Labor Organizations, 1958-1967 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Reunion, 1964 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Reunion of Old Timers, 1963 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1970-1972 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Rheinmetall: Slave Labor, 1965-1967 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Rhode Island, 1966 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Riesel, Victor, 1964-1968 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Riesel, Victor, 1969-1976 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Right-to-Work, 1962-1964 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Right-to-Work, 1976-1982 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Right-to-Work Law, 1978-1979 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Right-to-Work: Mailings, 1978-1979 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - Right-to-Work: Printed Material, 1976-1979 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Right-Wing Groups, 1960-1971 (Box 163, Folder 21-25)
  - Riots, 1967 (Box 163, Folder 26)
  - Rochester, NY, 1957-1959 (Box 163, Folder 27)
  - Rochester, NY, 1960 (Box 163, Folder 28)
  - Rochester, NY, 1961-1969 (Box 163, Folder 29)
  - Rochester, NY, 1963-1977 (Box 163, Folder 30)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 31)
  - Rockwell Question, 1963 (Box 163, Folder 32)
  - Romania, 1959-1961 (Box 163, Folder 33)
  - Romanian Jews, 1959 (Box 163, Folder 34)
  - Romanian Jews: Israel, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Romanian Relief Fund (Dubinsky), 1959 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Rubenstein, Jack (Textile Workers Union of America), 1966 (Box 164, Folder 2A)
  - Rumor Clinic, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1965-1979 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Rustin, Bayard: On Malcolm X, 1965 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers Labor Educational Center, 1980 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Rwanda, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Sabbath Observance and Employment, 1977-1980 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Sacramento, CA, 1963-1966 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Saint John's Strike, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Saint Louis, MO, 1958-1960 (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Saint Louis, MO, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - Saint Paul, MN, 1961-1962 (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Salute to Israel Parade, 1969-1972 (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1957-1976, undated (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - SANE (National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy): Trade Union Division, 1966-1967 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Santa Monica, CA, 1957 (Box 164, Folder 18)
  - Savanna, GA, 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1956-1958 (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 21)
  - Schlitt, Jacob, 1959-1963 (Box 164, Folder 22)
  - Schneersohn, Isaac, 1957 (Box 164, Folder 23)
  - Scholarship Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 164, Folder 24)
  - School Crisis, 1971-1973 (Box 164, Folder 25)
  - School Integration (New York City), 1956-1957, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 26-27)
  - School Integration (New York City and State), 1964-1965 (Box 164, Folder 28)
  - School Prayer, 1964 (Box 164, Folder 29-30)
  - Schools: Afro-American Teachers Association, 1972 (Box 164, Folder 31)
  - Schools: Charges of Subversion, 1951-1953 (Box 164, Folder 32)
  - Schools: Communist View, 1971 (Box 164, Folder 33)
  - Schools: NYC, 1964-1972 (Box 164, Folder 34)
  - Schools: NYC Decentralization, 1967-1970 (Box 164, Folder 35)
  - Schools: Non-Public: Tax Credits to Parents, 1972-1973 (Box 164, Folder 36)
  - Schools: Resolution on Public Education, Undated (Box 164, Folder 37)
  - Schools: Teachers' Strike (New York City), 1964-1969 (Box 164, Folder 38)
  - Schrager, P., 1977 (Box 164, Folder 39)
  - Scranton Commission, 1970-1971 (Box 164, Folder 40)
  - Screvane, Paul, 1963 (Box 164, Folder 41)
  - Segal, Ben, 1965 (Box 164, Folder 42)
  - Seliger, Ralph, 1973-1975 (Box 164, Folder 43)
  - Senior Citizens: Cavalcade, 1964 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Senior Citizens: Gold Ring Council, 1957-1968 (Box 165, Folder 2-5)
  - Senior Citizens: Lincoln Center Assembly, 1963 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Senior Citizens Rally, 1959-1960 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Senior, Clarence, 1967 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Sexton, Brendan, 1966 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1969-1976 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Sharecroppers Fund, 1967 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Shechita (Human Slaughter), 1970 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Sheinkman, Jacob: Articles and Speeches, 1978-1985 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - Sheinkman, Jacob: Biographical Information, 1974 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Sheinkman, Jacob: Correspondence, 1965, 1974-1982 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Sheinkman, Jacob: Report on Kissinger Meeting, Undated (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - Silberman, Charles, 1968 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - Silver Springs, MD, 1957-1958 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - Silver Springs, MD, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 19)